Gore Wang (王偉泰)

Front-End Engineer

Taipei, Taiwan

(=Welcome visit the web resume made by my own Gore Wang's Resume=)

Excellent organization and communication skills as well as experience of logical analysis, problem solving and creative realization.

Strong passion for product development, and localizing designs for a range of target markets. Able to use entrepreneurship experience to understand how details combine to affect product success.

Personally driven always to seek improvement, constantly evaluating goals in the pursuit of perfection.

SKILLS

Front-End Back-End

es6 | react | gsap(greensock) | a-frame(webvr) | sass(scss) | vue.js | angularjs(1) | rx.js | pug | nightwatch | chai | sinon mongodb(mongoose) | express

Tools Design

webpack | gulp | git | mercurial(hg) | npm

photoshop | illustrator (limited) | ptc creo elements/direct | pro/e

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Engineer at 燿麒科技 Lbstek

September 2015 - December 2016

New! L-somewhere: Website Development

- React + Redux
- Socket.io Chat Room
- Canvas Radar Animation
- Google/Baidu map customize
- i18n

Ease E-commercial: Website Development

- Production page
- Shopping Car

Weis Chinese Medicine Group:

- WebVR Develop (A-Frame)
- Official Website (Angular)

L-somewhere:

- New Graffiti (Angular)
- Website Maintenance (Django)

Design & Host at 謎攻城工作室 MGC Escape Room

May 2013 - June 2015

Planning, Production, Graphic Design, Website Design, Host, Video Editing

SPEAKING APPEARANCES

"WebVR vs Chinese" at Taipei WebGL&WebVR

05 Apr 2017

The strategy about render Chinese font in the WebVR.

"Draft.js" at 線上React讀書會

23 Mar 2017

- Youtube Video
- Discuss the structure of immutable data in Draft.js, and all decoration strategy.

"A-Frame WebVR" at Web Tech Topic

02 Dec 2016

A-Frame tutorial & experience sharing.

OPEN SOURCE / PUBLICATIONS

Stories Kingdom on GitHub

9 May 2017

- React, Express, Mongo, Mongoose, Draft.js, Webpack, Nightwatch, Chai, Sinon...
- The environment builds for vertical writing.
- 為了能在電腦撰寫中掌握中文直式排版的文韻,並保留傳統書頁「翻頁」產生的段落性閱讀節奏而撰寫的中文寫作平台。

A-frame chinese enhance component on GitHub

9 Apr 2017

- aframe-textwrap-component : CJ Unified Ideographs enhance version
- aframe-draw-component : Add background transparent property
- aframe-draw-component#stroke_text : Stroke text + CJ Unified Ideographs enhance version

Nuns on the run on GitHub

30 November 2016

- React, Express, Mongo, Socket.io, Canvas...
- Developed the gaming applications 'Nuns on the Run' for mobile phone and projector. Players cana take photos while the program adds virtual clothing onto the image.

Remiel on GitHub

2 September 2015

- jQuery, Gulp, SASS...
- Created the Chinese Novel Platform that enables users to add their own novels to share among the online community.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Electronics Engineering at National Chung Hsing University

COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

Taipei Voice Jam Hackathon at Mozilla

03 May 2017

Make the prototype which inspired from the Voice Jam.

VoiceBank: Voice Jam in Taipei at Mozilla

29 Apr 2017 - 30 Apr 2017

VoiceBank is a project to create an open dataset of people's voices. Then anyone can make new voice tools and help break the silos of the voice-enabled internet, ensuring we all have a voice in the internet's future. Join us this weekend to contribute to Mozilla VoiceBank project by making fun mobile experiences that encourage people to donate their voice.

Happy CSSer by Rplus

1 Jan 2017 - Now

Challenge to create some unique UI or animation by pure CSS.